

ROMAN KARPEYEV

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am a front-end developer and I have experience in creating SPA and dynamic webinterfaces.

I use the following tech stack: React, TypeScript/JavaScript, Redux.

I prefer to spend my free time on codewars.com or with educational books.

I enjoy what I do and I am focused on personal professional development.

EDUCATION

Mechatronics Engineering

Ida-Virumaa Kutsehariduskeskus

- Attended from Sept. 2013 to June 2017
- Mechatronics, Robotics, and Automation Engineering

SKILLS

JavaScript (ES5/ES6+), TypeScript, React.js, Redux, HTML, CSS(SASS/SCSS), REST API, Unit Tests Git(GitHub)

HOW TO REACH ME

- ☆ Ida-Virumaa, Estonia
- karpeyev.com
- (L) +372 58 329 597
- ♦ roman.karpeyev@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/insane4l
- github.com/insane4l

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Freelance · Apprenticeship May 2021 - present (8 mos)

- Creating web applications using React, Redux, TypeScript and SCSS (DAL, BLL, UI three-tier architecture).
- Code refactoring, bug fixing.
- Creating components.
- · Creating Unit Tests.
- Project migration from JavaScript to TypeScript.
- Translating the application from classes to functional components in accordance with the new standards.
- · Active Learning.

Web Developer

Freelance · Apprenticeship Jun 2020 - May 2021 (11 mos)

- Creating website layout interfaces from Figma, Avocode, Photoshop using HTML/SCSS/JS.
- Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.
- Product functionality testing.
- Active Learning.

Insulation worker, tinsmith BTIsolatsioon OÜ

Nov 2018 - Jun 2019 (8 mos)

- Install and replace the materials used to insulate mechanical systems.
- Teamwork Speaking, Coordination, Cooperation.
- Complex Problem Solving Identifying complex problems and reviewing related information to develop and evaluate options and implement solutions.
- Active Learning, Initiative personally challenging achievement goals and exerting effort toward mastering tasks. Willingness to take on responsibilities and challenges.